[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "name": "Team name 1",
        "owner": "0x385Eeac5cB85A38A9a07A70c73e0a3271CfB54A7",
        "leader": 1,
        "back1": 1,
        "back1Gotchi":
        {
            "id": 1,
            "onchainId": 1,
            "name": "PolterGeist",
            "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g1_front.svg",
            "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g1_back.svg",
            "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g1_left.svg",
            "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g1_right.svg",
            "brs": 569,
            "kinship": 829,
            "level": 6,
            "xp": 820,
            "nrg": 21,
            "agg": 79,
            "spk": 88,
            "brn": 76,
            "eys": 3,
            "eyc": 11,
            "availableSpecials":
            [
                {
                    "id": 1
                },
                {
                    "id": 4
                },
                {
                    "id": 5
                }
            ],
            "specialId": 1,
            "speed": 146,
            "health": 228,
            "accuracy": 71,
            "evade": 23,
            "physical": 150,
            "magic": 380,
            "armor": 1,
            "crit": 1,
            "resist": 0
        },
        "back2": null,
        "back2Gotchi": null,
        "back3": 2,
        "back3Gotchi":
        {
            "id": 2,
            "onchainId": 2,
            "name": "Testing Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String",
            "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g2_front.svg",
            "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g2_back.svg",
            "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g2_left.svg",
            "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g2_right.svg",
            "brs": 540,
            "kinship": 1000,
            "level": 3,
            "xp": 100,
            "nrg": -1,
            "agg": 0,
            "spk": 1,
            "brn": 99,
            "eys": 100,
            "eyc": 101,
            "availableSpecials":
            [
                {
                    "id": 7
                }
            ],
            "specialId": 7,
            "speed": 10,
            "health": 20,
            "accuracy": 30,
            "evade": 40,
            "physical": 50,
            "magic": 60,
            "armor": 70,
            "crit": 0,
            "resist": 80
        },
        "back4": null,
        "back4Gotchi": null,
        "back5": 4,
        "back5Gotchi":
        {
            "id": 4,
            "onchainId": 4,
            "name": "Casper",
            "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g4_front.svg",
            "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g4_back.svg",
            "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g4_left.svg",
            "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g4_right.svg",
            "brs": 500,
            "kinship": 5000,
            "level": 5,
            "xp": 5000,
            "nrg": 50,
            "agg": 50,
            "spk": 50,
            "brn": 50,
            "eys": 50,
            "eyc": 50,
            "availableSpecials":
            [
                {
                    "id": 6
                }
            ],
            "specialId": 6,
            "speed": 50,
            "health": 50,
            "accuracy": 50,
            "evade": 50,
            "physical": 50,
            "magic": 50,
            "armor": 50,
            "crit": 50,
            "resist": 50
        },
        "front1": null,
        "front1Gotchi": null,
        "front2": 3,
        "front2Gotchi":
        {
            "id": 3,
            "onchainId": 3,
            "name": "TestingLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWord",
            "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g3_front.svg",
            "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g3_back.svg",
            "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g3_left.svg",
            "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g3_right.svg",
            "brs": 0,
            "kinship": 0,
            "level": 0,
            "xp": 0,
            "nrg": 0,
            "agg": 0,
            "spk": 0,
            "brn": 0,
            "eys": 0,
            "eyc": 0,
            "availableSpecials":
            [
                {
                    "id": 1
                },
                {
                    "id": 2
                },
                {
                    "id": 3
                },
                {
                    "id": 4
                },
                {
                    "id": 5
                },
                {
                    "id": 6
                },
                {
                    "id": 7
                },
                {
                    "id": 8
                }
            ],
            "specialId": 8,
            "speed": 0,
            "health": 0,
            "accuracy": 0,
            "evade": 0,
            "physical": 0,
            "magic": 0,
            "armor": 0,
            "crit": 0,
            "resist": 0
        },
        "front3": null,
        "front3Gotchi": null,
        "front4": 5,
        "front4Gotchi":
        {
            "id": 5,
            "onchainId": 5,
            "name": "Orko",
            "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g5_front.svg",
            "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g5_back.svg",
            "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g5_left.svg",
            "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g5_right.svg",
            "brs": 520,
            "kinship": 1000,
            "level": 6,
            "xp": 820,
            "nrg": 4,
            "agg": 8,
            "spk": 15,
            "brn": 16,
            "eys": 23,
            "eyc": 42,
            "availableSpecials":
            [
                {
                    "id": 7
                },
                {
                    "id": 5
                }
            ],
            "specialId": 5,
            "speed": 146,
            "health": 228,
            "accuracy": 71,
            "evade": 23,
            "physical": 150,
            "magic": 380,
            "armor": 1,
            "crit": 1,
            "resist": 0
        },
        "front5": null,
        "front5Gotchi": null,
        "sub1": 6,
        "sub1Gotchi":
        {
            "id": 6,
            "onchainId": 6,
            "name": "Sir Humphrey",
            "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g6_front.svg",
            "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g6_back.svg",
            "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g6_left.svg",
            "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g6_right.svg",
            "brs": 569,
            "kinship": 829,
            "level": 6,
            "xp": 820,
            "nrg": 21,
            "agg": 79,
            "spk": 88,
            "brn": 76,
            "eys": 3,
            "eyc": 11,
            "availableSpecials":
            [
                {
                    "id": 1
                },
                {
                    "id": 4
                },
                {
                    "id": 5
                }
            ],
            "specialId": 4,
            "speed": 146,
            "health": 228,
            "accuracy": 71,
            "evade": 23,
            "physical": 150,
            "magic": 380,
            "armor": 1,
            "crit": 1,
            "resist": 0
        },
        "sub2": null,
        "sub2Gotchi": null
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "name": "Team name 2 Testing Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String",
        "owner": "0x86935F11C86623deC8a25696E1C19a8659CbF95d",
        "leader": 9,
        "back1": 6,
        "back1Gotchi":
        {
            "id": 6,
            "onchainId": 6,
            "name": "Nearly-Headless Nick",
            "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g6_front.svg",
            "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g6_back.svg",
            "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g6_left.svg",
            "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g6_right.svg",
            "brs": 500,
            "kinship": 5000,
            "level": 5,
            "xp": 5000,
            "nrg": 50,
            "agg": 50,
            "spk": 50,
            "brn": 50,
            "eys": 50,
            "eyc": 50,
            "availableSpecials":
            [
                {
                    "id": 3
                },
                {
                    "id": 2
                }
            ],
            "specialId": 3,
            "speed": 50,
            "health": 50,
            "accuracy": 50,
            "evade": 50,
            "physical": 50,
            "magic": 50,
            "armor": 50,
            "crit": 50,
            "resist": 50
        },
        "back2": 10,
        "back2Gotchi":
        {
            "id": 10,
            "onchainId": 10,
            "name": "Hopkirk",
            "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g10_front.svg",
            "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g10_back.svg",
            "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g10_left.svg",
            "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g10_right.svg",
            "brs": 500,
            "kinship": 5000,
            "level": 5,
            "xp": 5000,
            "nrg": 50,
            "agg": 50,
            "spk": 50,
            "brn": 50,
            "eys": 50,
            "eyc": 50,
            "availableSpecials":
            [
                {
                    "id": 2
                }
            ],
            "specialId": 2,
            "speed": 50,
            "health": 50,
            "accuracy": 50,
            "evade": 50,
            "physical": 50,
            "magic": 50,
            "armor": 50,
            "crit": 50,
            "resist": 50
        },
        "back3": 9,
        "back3Gotchi":
        {
            "id": 9,
            "onchainId": 9,
            "name": "Obi Wan Kenobi",
            "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g9_front.svg",
            "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g9_back.svg",
            "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g9_left.svg",
            "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g9_right.svg",
            "brs": 500,
            "kinship": 5000,
            "level": 5,
            "xp": 5000,
            "nrg": 50,
            "agg": 50,
            "spk": 50,
            "brn": 50,
            "eys": 50,
            "eyc": 50,
            "availableSpecials":
            [
                {
                    "id": 7
                }
            ],
            "specialId": 7,
            "speed": 50,
            "health": 50,
            "accuracy": 50,
            "evade": 50,
            "physical": 50,
            "magic": 50,
            "armor": 50,
            "crit": 50,
            "resist": 50
        },
        "back4": 7,
        "back4Gotchi":
        {
            "id": 7,
            "onchainId": 7,
            "name": "Moaning Myrtle",
            "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g7_front.svg",
            "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g7_back.svg",
            "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g7_left.svg",
            "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g7_right.svg",
            "brs": 500,
            "kinship": 5000,
            "level": 5,
            "xp": 5000,
            "nrg": 50,
            "agg": 50,
            "spk": 50,
            "brn": 50,
            "eys": 50,
            "eyc": 50,
            "availableSpecials":
            [
                {
                    "id": 7
                },
                {
                    "id": 4
                }
            ],
            "specialId": 4,
            "speed": 50,
            "health": 50,
            "accuracy": 50,
            "evade": 50,
            "physical": 50,
            "magic": 50,
            "armor": 50,
            "crit": 50,
            "resist": 50
        },
        "back5": 8,
        "back5Gotchi":
        {
            "id": 8,
            "onchainId": 8,
            "name": "Peeves",
            "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g8_front.svg",
            "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g8_back.svg",
            "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g8_left.svg",
            "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g8_right.svg",
            "brs": 500,
            "kinship": 5000,
            "level": 5,
            "xp": 5000,
            "nrg": 50,
            "agg": 50,
            "spk": 50,
            "brn": 50,
            "eys": 50,
            "eyc": 50,
            "availableSpecials":
            [
                {
                    "id": 8
                }
            ],
            "specialId": 8,
            "speed": 50,
            "health": 50,
            "accuracy": 50,
            "evade": 50,
            "physical": 50,
            "magic": 50,
            "armor": 50,
            "crit": 50,
            "resist": 50
        },
        "front1": null,
        "front1Gotchi": null,
        "front2": null,
        "front2Gotchi": null,
        "front3": null,
        "front3Gotchi": null,
        "front4": null,
        "front4Gotchi": null,
        "front5": null,
        "front5Gotchi": null
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "name": "Team name 3 TestingLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWord",
        "owner": "0x86935F11C86623deC8a25696E1C19a8659CbF95d"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "name": "Team name 4 - Test my team",
        "owner": "0xBfe09443556773958bae1699b786d8E9680B5571"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "name": "Team name 5",
        "owner": "0x385Eeac5cB85A38A9a07A70c73e0a3271CfB54A7"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "name": "Team name 6 - another one with my address",
        "owner": "0xBfe09443556773958bae1699b786d8E9680B5571"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "name": "Team name 7",
        "owner": "0x3F382DbD960E3a9bbCeaE22651E88158d2791550"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "name": "Team name 8",
        "owner": "0x385Eeac5cB85A38A9a07A70c73e0a3271CfB54A7"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "name": "Team name 9",
        "owner": "0x1906fd9c4AC440561F7197Da0A4BD2E88DF5fA70"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "name": "Team name 10",
        "owner": "0x1906fd9c4AC440561F7197Da0A4BD2E88DF5fA70"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "name": "Team name 11",
        "owner": "0x58de9AaBCaeEC0f69883C94318810ad79Cc6a44f"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "name": "Team name 12",
        "owner": "0x58de9AaBCaeEC0f69883C94318810ad79Cc6a44f"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "name": "Team name 13",
        "owner": "0x58de9AaBCaeEC0f69883C94318810ad79Cc6a44f"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "name": "Team name 14",
        "owner": "0x1906fd9c4AC440561F7197Da0A4BD2E88DF5fA70"
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "name": "Team name 15",
        "owner": "0x1906fd9c4AC440561F7197Da0A4BD2E88DF5fA70"
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "name": "Team name 16",
        "owner": "0x3F382DbD960E3a9bbCeaE22651E88158d2791550"
    },
    {
        "id": 0,
        "name": "Team 0",
        "owner": "0xd8D4BDb89D64B7A2971Dc987DD67F101fea6c7D8"
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "name": "Mock Team 17",
        "owner": "0xd8D4BDb89D64B7A2971Dc987DD67F101fea6c7D8",
        "leader": 231,
        "back1": 233,
        "back1Gotchi":
        {
            "id": 233,
            "onchainId": 233,
            "name": "Drop It Like It's Hot",
            "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g9_front.svg",
            "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g9_back.svg",
            "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g9_left.svg",
            "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g9_right.svg",
            "brs": 0,
            "kinship": 0,
            "level": 0,
            "xp": 0,
            "nrg": 0,
            "agg": 0,
            "spk": 0,
            "brn": 0,
            "eys": 0,
            "eyc": 0,
            "availableSpecials":
            [
                {
                    "id": 1
                },
                {
                    "id": 2
                },
                {
                    "id": 3
                },
                {
                    "id": 4
                },
                {
                    "id": 5
                },
                {
                    "id": 6
                },
                {
                    "id": 7
                },
                {
                    "id": 8
                }
            ],
            "specialId": 8,
            "speed": 0,
            "health": 0,
            "accuracy": 0,
            "evade": 0,
            "physical": 0,
            "magic": 0,
            "armor": 0,
            "crit": 1,
            "resist": 0
        },
        "back2": 230,
        "back2Gotchi":
        {
            "id": 230,
            "onchainId": 230,
            "name": "",
            "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g2_front.svg",
            "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g2_back.svg",
            "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g2_left.svg",
            "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g2_right.svg",
            "brs": 569,
            "kinship": 829,
            "level": 6,
            "xp": 820,
            "nrg": 21,
            "agg": 79,
            "spk": 88,
            "brn": 76,
            "eys": 3,
            "eyc": 11,
            "availableSpecials":
            [
                {
                    "id": 1
                },
                {
                    "id": 4
                },
                {
                    "id": 5
                }
            ],
            "specialId": 1,
            "speed": 146,
            "health": 228,
            "accuracy": 71,
            "evade": 23,
            "physical": 150,
            "magic": 380,
            "armor": 1,
            "crit": 1,
            "resist": 0
        },
        "back3": null,
        "back3Gotchi": null,
        "back4": 232,
        "back4Gotchi":
        {
            "id": 232,
            "onchainId": 232,
            "name": "",
            "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g6_front.svg",
            "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g6_back.svg",
            "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g6_left.svg",
            "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g6_right.svg",
            "brs": 500,
            "kinship": 5000,
            "level": 5,
            "xp": 5000,
            "nrg": 50,
            "agg": 50,
            "spk": 50,
            "brn": 50,
            "eys": 50,
            "eyc": 50,
            "availableSpecials":
            [
                {
                    "id": 6
                }
            ],
            "specialId": 6,
            "speed": 50,
            "health": 50,
            "accuracy": 50,
            "evade": 50,
            "physical": 50,
            "magic": 50,
            "armor": 50,
            "crit": 50,
            "resist": 50
        },
        "back5": 231,
        "back5Gotchi":
        {
            "id": 231,
            "onchainId": 231,
            "name": "Lead",
            "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g10_front.svg",
            "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g10_back.svg",
            "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g10_left.svg",
            "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g10_right.svg",
            "brs": 540,
            "kinship": 1000,
            "level": 3,
            "xp": 100,
            "nrg": -1,
            "agg": 0,
            "spk": 1,
            "brn": 99,
            "eys": 100,
            "eyc": 101,
            "availableSpecials":
            [
                {
                    "id": 7
                }
            ],
            "specialId": 7,
            "speed": 10,
            "health": 20,
            "accuracy": 30,
            "evade": 40,
            "physical": 50,
            "magic": 60,
            "armor": 70,
            "crit": 1,
            "resist": 80
        },
        "front1": null,
        "front1Gotchi": null,
        "front2": null,
        "front2Gotchi": null,
        "front3": 234,
        "front3Gotchi":
        {
            "id": 234,
            "onchainId": 234,
            "name": "I believe",
            "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g10_front.svg",
            "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g10_back.svg",
            "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g10_left.svg",
            "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g10_right.svg",
            "brs": 520,
            "kinship": 1000,
            "level": 6,
            "xp": 820,
            "nrg": 4,
            "agg": 8,
            "spk": 15,
            "brn": 16,
            "eys": 23,
            "eyc": 42,
            "availableSpecials":
            [
                {
                    "id": 7
                },
                {
                    "id": 5
                }
            ],
            "specialId": 5,
            "speed": 146,
            "health": 228,
            "accuracy": 71,
            "evade": 23,
            "physical": 150,
            "magic": 380,
            "armor": 1,
            "crit": 1,
            "resist": 0
        },
        "front4": null,
        "front4Gotchi": null,
        "front5": null,
        "front5Gotchi": null
    },
    {
        "id": 21,
        "name": "Mock Team 21",
        "owner": "0xd8D4BDb89D64B7A2971Dc987DD67F101fea6c7D8",
        "leader": 189,
        "back1": null,
        "back1Gotchi": null,
        "back2": null,
        "back2Gotchi": null,
        "back3": null,
        "back3Gotchi": null,
        "back4": null,
        "back4Gotchi": null,
        "back5": null,
        "back5Gotchi": null,
        "front1": 201,
        "front1Gotchi":
        {
            "id": 201,
            "onchainId": 201,
            "name": "VIDRUT",
            "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g2_front.svg",
            "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g2_back.svg",
            "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g2_left.svg",
            "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g2_right.svg",
            "brs": 569,
            "kinship": 829,
            "level": 6,
            "xp": 820,
            "nrg": 21,
            "agg": 79,
            "spk": 88,
            "brn": 76,
            "eys": 3,
            "eyc": 11,
            "availableSpecials":
            [
                {
                    "id": 1
                },
                {
                    "id": 4
                },
                {
                    "id": 5
                }
            ],
            "specialId": 1,
            "speed": 146,
            "health": 228,
            "accuracy": 71,
            "evade": 23,
            "physical": 150,
            "magic": 380,
            "armor": 1,
            "crit": 1,
            "resist": 0
        },
        "front2": 188,
        "front2Gotchi":
        {
            "id": 188,
            "onchainId": 188,
            "name": "ALPHASAURUS REX",
            "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g9_front.svg",
            "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g9_back.svg",
            "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g9_left.svg",
            "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g9_right.svg",
            "brs": 0,
            "kinship": 0,
            "level": 0,
            "xp": 0,
            "nrg": 0,
            "agg": 0,
            "spk": 0,
            "brn": 0,
            "eys": 0,
            "eyc": 0,
            "availableSpecials":
            [
                {
                    "id": 1
                },
                {
                    "id": 2
                },
                {
                    "id": 3
                },
                {
                    "id": 4
                },
                {
                    "id": 5
                },
                {
                    "id": 6
                },
                {
                    "id": 7
                },
                {
                    "id": 8
                }
            ],
            "specialId": 8,
            "speed": 0,
            "health": 0,
            "accuracy": 0,
            "evade": 0,
            "physical": 0,
            "magic": 0,
            "armor": 0,
            "crit": 1,
            "resist": 0
        },
        "front3": 189,
        "front3Gotchi":
        {
            "id": 189,
            "onchainId": 189,
            "name": "Bear Market",
            "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g10_front.svg",
            "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g10_back.svg",
            "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g10_left.svg",
            "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g10_right.svg",
            "brs": 540,
            "kinship": 1000,
            "level": 3,
            "xp": 100,
            "nrg": -1,
            "agg": 0,
            "spk": 1,
            "brn": 99,
            "eys": 100,
            "eyc": 101,
            "availableSpecials":
            [
                {
                    "id": 7
                }
            ],
            "specialId": 7,
            "speed": 10,
            "health": 20,
            "accuracy": 30,
            "evade": 40,
            "physical": 50,
            "magic": 60,
            "armor": 70,
            "crit": 1,
            "resist": 80
        },
        "front4": 199,
        "front4Gotchi":
        {
            "id": 199,
            "onchainId": 199,
            "name": "Defiant",
            "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g10_front.svg",
            "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g10_back.svg",
            "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g10_left.svg",
            "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g10_right.svg",
            "brs": 520,
            "kinship": 1000,
            "level": 6,
            "xp": 820,
            "nrg": 4,
            "agg": 8,
            "spk": 15,
            "brn": 16,
            "eys": 23,
            "eyc": 42,
            "availableSpecials":
            [
                {
                    "id": 7
                },
                {
                    "id": 5
                }
            ],
            "specialId": 5,
            "speed": 146,
            "health": 228,
            "accuracy": 71,
            "evade": 23,
            "physical": 150,
            "magic": 380,
            "armor": 1,
            "crit": 1,
            "resist": 0
        },
        "front5": 235,
        "front5Gotchi":
        {
            "id": 235,
            "onchainId": 235,
            "name": "Sunny",
            "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g6_front.svg",
            "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g6_back.svg",
            "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g6_left.svg",
            "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g6_right.svg",
            "brs": 500,
            "kinship": 5000,
            "level": 5,
            "xp": 5000,
            "nrg": 50,
            "agg": 50,
            "spk": 50,
            "brn": 50,
            "eys": 50,
            "eyc": 50,
            "availableSpecials":
            [
                {
                    "id": 6
                }
            ],
            "specialId": 6,
            "speed": 50,
            "health": 50,
            "accuracy": 50,
            "evade": 50,
            "physical": 50,
            "magic": 50,
            "armor": 50,
            "crit": 50,
            "resist": 50
        }
    }
]